ILGWU Research Department Records 5780/168
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Educational Work, ILGWU, 1935-1950; Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Item 39: C.I.O. Calls Labor To Action!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
    By Educational Dep't, Dressmakers Union Local 22, I. L. G. W. U. Thursday, February 10 (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 40: An Important Message To Our Members, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
    By Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10 Educational Department. Beginning Wednesday, October 14, 1936-1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Student's Card, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
    By Educational Department. 1919-1920. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Important Information for Cloakmakers Employed in New York State Regarding Disability Benefits, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
    By Joint Board Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Unions International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union - A.F.L. Beginnging July 1, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Education Program 1947-48, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
    By Educational Department, ILGWU. Starts October 7/8. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Women's Garment Industry, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Item 45: The Garment Workers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Item 46: Canned Pins and Needles I.L.G.W.U. Victrola Records, Publication (Box 11, Folder 24)
- ILGWU Union Label Dept., Promotional Material, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Find the Union Label in this Garment Win, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). A blouse a day will be award commencing August 1st, 1969, until December 12th, 1969. Item is in English; French.
  - Item 2: Look for the Luck Label in this Garment Win, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). April 30, May 15/31, June 28, July 31, August 30, October 10, Contest closes September 30, 1968. Item is in English; French.
  - Item 3: Right as Rain, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Dany, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)/M O D E R N Talking Pictures. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Vos Mesures S.V.P., Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Item is in French.
  - Item 6: The Size of It, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: To be Health and Slim/Pour etre en pliene forme et Suelte, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Unknown Date. Item is in French; English.
  - Item 8: 60-Second Test for Smart Shoppers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: Acme Waitress Decal, Publication (Box 11, Folder 25)
    By Acme Decalomania Ltd. Item is in French; English.
- Radio Campaign, 1974; Publication (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: I.L.G.W.U. Schedule on Wins, Publication (Box 11, Folder 26)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). November 11-15, 1974. Item is in English.
- Radio Campaign (add'l), 1973-1974; Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Copy #10 Approved, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). November 21, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Radio Package Plans - I.L.G.W.U. - Union Label, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). February 14, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: I.L.G.W.U. WINS-AM, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). April 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: I.L.G.W.U. - WINS Schedule - Week of April 1, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). March 29, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Typical ILGWU Schedule on WINS, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
    By New From 1010 WINS. March 11, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The I.L.G.W.U. Message Will Be on the Air 50 Times A Week, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). March 22, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: I.L.G.W.U. - Union Label - Spring Radio Campaign, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). January 29, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Radio - Fall '74, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
    Use November 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: You Union Reports, Publication (Box 11, Folder 27)
    By Gus Tyler for the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Unknown Date. Item is in English.
- ILGWU, NYC, Dressmaker's Union, 1936-1947; Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Watch Your Minimums, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Joint Board Dress and Waistmakers Union. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: General Demands, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Estimated Number of Non-Union Workers, by Occupation, in Shops Controlled by the N.Y. Joint Board, Dress & Waistmakers Union, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By N.Y. Joint Board, Dress & Waistmakers Union. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Dressmakers! General Strike Declared!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Waist and Dressmakers' Union, I.L.G.W.U. March 5, 1947. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 5: Age of Membership Locals 10, 22, 60 and 89, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Joint Board Dress & Waistmakers' Union. November 30, 1946. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 6: Outline of Union's Demands, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Unknown Author/Date. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 7: Dollar Volume of Business and Number of Garments Produced by the Dress Industry, New York Market, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Joint Board of the Dress & Waistmakers' Union. 1939 - 1946. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 8: Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By New York Dress Joint Board. December10, 1946. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 9: Dress Union Refuses 1 Year Pact Extention, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Item 10: For Immediate Release, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Herman Wolf, Dress Joint Board. Tuesday, December 10/17, 1940,. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 11: For Release AM & PM Newspapers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Dress Joint Board. Wednesday, January 28/29th, 1941. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 12: Historic Agreement Signed at City Hall Between Union and Dress Employers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Herman Wolf, Dress Joint Board. Ruesday February 18, 1941. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 13: Impartial Chairman in Dress Industry Announces New Efficiency Rules., Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Dress Joint Board. PM Papers Thursday July 24, 1941, AM Papers Friday July 25, 1941. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 14: Attention: Messrs. Wm. Green, David Dubinsky, Frank Crosswaith, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By The Workers Council of Harlem. Unknown Date. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 15: Dressmakers of North Hudson County Come to the Mass Shop Conference, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Dress Department, Needle Trades Workers Industrial Union. Friday - August 11th, (Unknown Year). Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 16: Dressmakers of Harlem, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Central Committee Left Wing Groups in ILGWU. Sunday January 6th (Unknown Year). Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 17: Proclamation and Manifesto, Publication (Box 11, Folder 28)
    By Morris Sigman. "The agreement between the Union and the Employers in the Dress Industry expires on December 31, 1926". Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU Local 91, 1937-1947; Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Dressmakers! General Strike Declared!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By General Strike Committee of the Joint Board, Waist and Dressmakers' Union, I.L.G.W.U. March 5, 1947. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 2: Annual Report for the Year 1938, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Harry Greenberg. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Local 91 Art Workshop, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Educational Department Children's Dress, Housedress and Bathrobe Makers' Union. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Local 91 Sings!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Educational Department, Local 91, I.L.G.W.U. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Report for the Year 1937 on the Sick Benefit Plan of the Children's Dress, Infants' Wear, Housedress amd Bathrobe Makers' Union Local 91, I.L.G.W.U., Publication (Box 11, Folder 29)
    By Leo Price, M.D. December, 1938. Item is in English.
- Organizational Leaflets, ILGWU Local 32, 1962; Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Workers of Marcus & Weisen! These Conditions Must Be Changed, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By Corset & Brassiere Workers Union I.L.G.W.U. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Workers of Marcus & Weisen Don't Let Your Boss Get Away With It!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By Corset & Brassiere Workers Union Local #32, I.L.G.W.U. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Workers of Gluckin, Inc., Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By Corset & Brassiere Workers Union, Local 32, I.L.G.W.U. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Workers of Gluckin Corp.!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By Corset & Brassiere Workers Union, Local 32, I.L.G.W.U. "Will 1935 be a btter year for you than 1934???". Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Important Notice To all Corset & Brassiere Workers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By Executive Board Corset & Brassiere Workers' Union, Local 32, I.L.G.W.U. Thursday, December 12, 1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Timely Message To all Corset & Brassiere Workers of Gr. N.Y., Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By Corset and Brassiere Workers Union Local 32, I. L. G. W. U. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Corset & Brassiere Workers of Greater New York The Season Is On, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: Corset & Brassiere Workers of Gr. N.Y. Remember These Promises!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By Corset and Brassiere Workers Union Local 32, I. L. G. W. U. "last Sptember" Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Dedication of the ILGWU Cooperative Houses, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). May 19, 1962. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Corset and Brassiere Workers Will It Be a Happy New Year? This is of Interest to You, Publication (Box 11, Folder 30)
    By Corset and Brassiere Workers' Union Local 32, I. L. G. W. U. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
- ILGWU, Local 10, 1938; Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Watch Out Cutters!!!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    By Cutters Trade Union Campaign Committee. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Taylor's Well-Fit Program, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    By Taylor for Manager of Local #10. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Bitter Union Local Fight Nearing Close, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). February 16, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Local 10 Suspended Members' Plea Denied, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    November 27, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Nagler Heads Cutters' Local, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    February 20, 1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Cutters Local 10 to Hold Election Feb. 18, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    January 24, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Would Advance Cutters' Election, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    January 17, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Nagler, Perlmutter Nominated by Cutters, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    January 31, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Suspended Members Of Local 10 File Suit Asking Reinstatement, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    October 11, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: 7 Dropped By Union Adk Dubinsky's Aid, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    January 21, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Nagler Is Honored By Cloak Joint Board, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    December 6, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Cutters of Local 10 Continue to Guard Your Union!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    By Cutters Union Local 10. Saturday, Match 15, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: An Appeal by the Progressive Cutters League of Local No. 10, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    By Progressive Cutters League of Local No. 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: A Warning to the Cutters of Local 10, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    By A Group of Members of the Cutters Branch 10-A of The Jewish National Workers Alliance. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Sad Case of Mr. Nagler, "The Man Nobody Wants", Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    By Cutter Trade Union Campaign Committee of One Thousand. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Samuel Perlmutter as Manager of Local 10 and a New Administration, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    By Cutters Trade Union Campaign Committee of One Thousand. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: From the Archives of Local 10 - The March of The Stooges!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    By Cutter's Trade Union Campaign Committee. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Let's Look At the Record, Publication (Box 11, Folder 31)
    By United Administration Campaign Committee Cutters Union, Local 10. Monday, February 24/Saturday, March 15 (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
- ILGWU, Local 22, 1946; Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: 7 Million Allies, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
    By Charles S. Zimmerman, Dressmakers Union Local 22, ILGWU. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Declaration of the Industrial Union to all Dressmakers of Loc. 22, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
    By Needle Trades Workers Industrial Union. Item is in English; Yiddish.
  - Item 3: Dressmakers of Local 22, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
    By Left Wing of Local 22, I.L.G.W.U. Item is in English; Yiddish.
  - Item 4: Dressmakers of Local 22-Negro and White Facts Speak Louder Than Words, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
    By The Left Wing of Local 22 I.L.G.W.U. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: La Union Al Trabajo, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
    By Dressmakers Union, Local 22 I.L.G.W.U. April 17, 1934. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 6: Learn and Play in Your Union, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
    By Lewis Corey, Educational Department Dressmakers Union, Local 22, I.L.G.W.U. Fall 1938 Catalog. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: To All Dressmakers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
    By Communist Party - New York District. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Dressmakers of Local 22, I.L.G.W.U. Here Is The Real Face of the Zimmerman Fake Progressives!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Item 9: Dressmakers of the I. L. G. W. U. Come to an Open Meeting of the Left Wing Group Local 22, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
    By Left Wing Group, Local 22, I.L.G.W.U. Item is in English; Yiddish.
  - Item 10: Declaration of 69 Dress Shop Groups, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
    By Left Wing Local 22. Item is in English; Yiddish.
  - Item 11: Dressmakers of Loc. 22 The Conspiracy of Zimmerman and the Dress Bosses Exposed!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 32)
    By Left Wing of Local 22, I.L.G.W.U. Monday March 19 (Unknown Year). Item is in English; Yiddish.
- Organizational Leaflets, Jt. Board, Cloakmakers Union, NYC, 1937-1947; Publication (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Election Call!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 33)
    By Executive Board, Local 117, ILGWU. Unknown Date. Item is in English; Yiddish.
  - Item 2: Attention! Cloak Drivers and Helpers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 33)
    By Cloak Drivers and Helpers' Union. Local 102, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: L1-NY, Publication (Box 11, Folder 33)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Item is in Yiddish.
  - Item 4: Second Annual Dinner in Honor of the Building Chairmen of the Dress Industry, Publication (Box 11, Folder 33)
    By Joint Board of the Dress and Waistmakers' Union. March 12, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Financial Report of the General Strike of the Ladies' Waist and Dress Makers' Union Local 25 I. L. G. W. U., Publication (Box 11, Folder 33)
    By F. Nathan Wolf, General Auditor, I.L.G.W.U. 1919 (Not When Written). Item is in English; Yiddish.
  - Item 6: The New Post - The General Strike Declared To All Cloak and Skirt Makers of Greater New York and Vicinity!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 33)
    By General Executive Board of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. The Joint Board of the Cloak and Skirt Makers' Union of New York and Vicinity. Wednesday, May 3, 1916. Item is in Yiddish; English; Italian.
- Jt. Board, Dress and Waistmakers Union, NYC, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: To All Dressmakers Operators, Finishers, Drapers, Examiners and Cleaners, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Dressmakers' Union, Local, No. 22, I.L.G.W.U. Unknown Date. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 2: Dressmakers Next! Victory of Cloakmakers Signal for Campaign to Organize Dressmakers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Joint Board Cloak, Suit, Skirt, Dress & Reefer Makers Union. Sunday, July 14, 1929. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 3: Dressmakers Lose No Time!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Joint Board Dress & Waist Makers' Union I. L. G. W. U. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 4: Dressmakers! Fall in Line! Prepare for the General Strike, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Joint Board Dress & Waistmakers' Union I L. G. W. U. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 5: Abolish The Auction Block, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Joint Board Dress & Waistmakers' Union I.L. G. W. U. Thursday, February 4th 1932. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 6: Nice Buildings, But-- Sweat Shops Just The Same, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Joint Board Cloak & Dressmakers Union. Unknown Date. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 7: Dressmakers Destroy This Monster!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Joint Board Dress & Waistmakers' Union I. L. G. W. A. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 8: White Goods Workers of Greater New York & Brooklyn A General Strike is Declared!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By General Executive Board, I. L. G. W. U. Amalg. Ladies' Garment Cutters Union, Local 10 White Goods Workers Union, Local 62. Tuesday, March 20, 1923. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 9: Plain Talk, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Julius Hochman, Joint Board Dress & Waistmakers' Union. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Waist and Dressmakers' General Strike Declared, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Joint Board Waist and Dressmakers' Union, Locals 50 and 71, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Tuesday May 9th, 1933. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 11: To All Dressmakers of Open Shops, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Joint Board Dress & Waistmakers' Union I. L. G. W. U. Unknown Date. Item is in English; Yiddish.
  - Item 12: The "Sweat Shop" and "Corporation Shop" in the Cloak Industry Must Go!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Joint Board Cloak, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Union, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Tuesday, July 25, 1922. Item is in Yiddish; English; Italian.
  - Item 13: General Strike Declared, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Local 38 International Ladies Garment Workers Union. Thursday, September 25, 1930. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Supreme Court Decision Does Not Affect Dressmakers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Julius Hochman, General Manager, Joint Board Dress & Waistmakers' Union. August 16th/19th, 1933. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 15: New York Dress Joint Board Its Composition, Functions and Structure, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Nathaniel M. Minkoff, Sec.-Treas. December 19, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Organizer - Vote for the General Strike, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Joint Board Dress & Waistmakers' Union. November 13, 1947. Item is in English; Yiddish.
  - Item 17: Dressmakers, Prepare!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Joint Board Dress and Waist Makers' Union. November 13, 1947. Item is in English; Italian; Yiddish.
  - Item 18: Jobbers Present A "Code" Dressmakers Prepare for Strike, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Item 19: Dress Campaign in Full Swing!!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Joint Board Dress and Waist Makers' Union. November 13, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: International Starts Campaign to Organize All Dressmakers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By Joint Board Dress and Waist Makers' Union, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. November 11, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: 5780/168 Add'l (Accessioned 10.24.99), Publication (Box 11, Folder 34)
    By ILGWU Research Department. October 24, 1999. Item is in English.
- ILGWU Training Institute, 1950-1954; Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: David Dubinsky Cordially Invites ___ to Attend the Official Opening of the Training Institute of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Monday, May 1, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Graduation International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Training Institute Class of 1958, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Thursday, June 5th, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Graduation International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Training Institute Class of 1954, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Thursday, May 27, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Plan and Program International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Training Institute, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    By Arthur A. Eldor. November 16 - early in 1950 - May 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Strike Publicity/Labor Publicity, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    By Frank Palmer/Richard Rohman. February 24, 1936. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Negotiation and Enforcement Problems, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    By David Dubinsky. March 2, 1936/ February 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: ILDWU Training Institute Script, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Wednesday, February 17, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: 16mm Sound Films Available to ILGWU Locals From Educational Department, ILGWU, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    By Mark Starr. November 16, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Report of the ILGWU Institute, Hudson View Lodge, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    June 13-15/25, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Developing Men Through Unions, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    By Nicholas Kirtzman. May 6, 1952/June 19, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: New York Dress Joint Board Its Composition, Functions and Structure, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    By Nathaniel M. Minkoff. February, 29, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The ILGWU Legal Department, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)
    By Morris P. Glushien. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Garment Workers, Publication (Box 11, Folder 35)